[{"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [6, 9, 3, 7, 10, 8], "content": ["与1最接近", "与2最接近", "距离4最远"]}], "answers": [3, 3, 10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [0, 9, 6, 3, 7, 8], "content": ["与1最接近", "与2最接近", "距离10最远"]}], "answers": [0, 3, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [4, 6, 3, 7, 10, 5], "content": ["与1最接近", "与9最接近", "距离2最远"]}], "answers": [3, 10, 10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [3, 5, 4, 0, 8, 7], "content": ["与1最接近", "与9最接近", "距离10最远"]}], "answers": [0, 8, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [5, 0, 4, 6, 8, 7], "content": ["与1最接近", "与10最接近", "距离9最远"]}], "answers": [0, 8, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [5, 4, 10, 7, 8, 9], "content": ["与2最接近", "与1最接近", "距离3最远"]}], "answers": [4, 4, 10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [9, 7, 10, 0, 5, 6], "content": ["与2最接近", "与1最接近", "距离4最远"]}], "answers": [0, 0, 10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [10, 4, 5, 9, 6, 7], "content": ["与3最接近", "与1最接近", "距离2最远"]}], "answers": [4, 4, 10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [7, 9, 10, 5, 0, 8], "content": ["与3最接近", "与2最接近", "距离1最远"]}], "answers": [5, 0, 10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [10, 5, 6, 8, 7, 9], "content": ["与3最接近", "与4最接近", "距离2最远"]}], "answers": [5, 5, 10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [5, 9, 6, 10, 8, 7], "content": ["与4最接近", "与2最接近", "距离3最远"]}], "answers": [5, 5, 10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [1, 4, 2, 3, 5, 0], "content": ["与6最接近", "与7最接近", "距离8最远"]}], "answers": [5, 5, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [8, 3, 5, 0, 1, 2], "content": ["与6最接近", "与7最接近", "距离10最远"]}], "answers": [5, 8, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [5, 3, 0, 2, 4, 1], "content": ["与6最接近", "与9最接近", "距离7最远"]}], "answers": [5, 5, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [0, 5, 2, 1, 8, 3], "content": ["与7最接近", "与6最接近", "距离10最远"]}], "answers": [8, 5, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [2, 0, 10, 1, 9, 3], "content": ["与7最接近", "与8最接近", "距离4最远"]}], "answers": [9, 9, 10], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [8, 3, 5, 1, 0, 2], "content": ["与7最接近", "与10最接近", "距离6最远"]}], "answers": [8, 8, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [2, 0, 5, 3, 4, 6], "content": ["与7最接近", "与10最接近", "距离8最远"]}], "answers": [6, 6, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [4, 0, 7, 2, 1, 6], "content": ["与8最接近", "与9最接近", "距离10最远"]}], "answers": [7, 7, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [0, 7, 2, 6, 3, 5], "content": ["与8最接近", "与10最接近", "距离9最远"]}], "answers": [7, 7, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [4, 8, 6, 5, 3, 0], "content": ["与9最接近", "与1最接近", "距离10最远"]}], "answers": [8, 0, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [8, 7, 4, 5, 3, 6], "content": ["与9最接近", "与2最接近", "距离10最远"]}], "answers": [8, 3, 3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [0, 5, 1, 3, 7, 4], "content": ["与9最接近", "与8最接近", "距离10最远"]}], "answers": [7, 7, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [0, 3, 2, 5, 6, 4], "content": ["与9最接近", "与10最接近", "距离8最远"]}], "answers": [6, 6, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [7, 0, 5, 8, 6, 9], "content": ["与10最接近", "与1最接近", "距离2最远"]}], "answers": [9, 0, 9], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [7, 5, 8, 9, 0, 6], "content": ["与10最接近", "与2最接近", "距离1最远"]}], "answers": [9, 0, 9], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [8, 7, 6, 5, 2, 9], "content": ["与10最接近", "与3最接近", "距离1最远"]}], "answers": [9, 2, 9], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [0, 1, 5, 3, 6, 4], "content": ["与10最接近", "与7最接近", "距离8最远"]}], "answers": [6, 6, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [3, 6, 1, 2, 4, 0], "content": ["与10最接近", "与7最接近", "距离9最远"]}], "answers": [6, 6, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [1, 0, 3, 2, 5, 4], "content": ["与10最接近", "与8最接近", "距离7最远"]}], "answers": [5, 5, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [3, 6, 0, 1, 5, 2], "content": ["与10最接近", "与8最接近", "距离9最远"]}], "answers": [6, 6, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [4, 8, 6, 0, 3, 5], "content": ["与10最接近", "与9最接近", "距离1最远"]}], "answers": [8, 8, 8], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [1, 3, 2, 5, 0, 6], "content": ["与10最接近", "与9最接近", "距离7最远"]}], "answers": [6, 6, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "near-number", "title": "填一填", "stem": "上面几个数字中", "list": [0, 3, 2, 1, 7, 5], "content": ["与10最接近", "与9最接近", "距离8最远"]}], "answers": [7, 7, 0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-10-09"}]